그러니까 엄마가 뭐라든
And that's why,
no matter what Mommy says..
아빠 엄마는
그때 냉각기였단다! 아무렴!
we really were on a break.
Yes, we were.
그렇구말구!
이리온, 우리 아기!
Yes, we were.
Come here, gorgeous.
우리 엠마!
세상에서 제일 예쁜 아기!
Look at you.
You are the cutest little baby ever.
우리 귀염둥이!
You're just a little-bitty baby,
you know that? But you've got..
눈이 아주 크고 예쁘지
You've got big, beautiful eyes.
그렇구 말구!
우리 아기 배도 크고
Yes, you do. And a..
And a big, round belly.
엉덩이도 아주 커요!
Big baby butt.
난 큰 엉덩이가 좋아
I like big butts.
거짓말은 못해
너희들도 부인 못할걸
개미허리 아가씨가
내게 다가오면 난..
세상에! 우리 엠마 웃었네!
Oh, my God, Emma.
You're laughing.
너 전엔 웃은적 없지?
처음 웃은거지?
Oh, my God. You've never
done that before, have you?
그래, 처음이야!
아빠가 우리 엠마 웃겼구나?
You've never done that before.
Daddy made you laugh, huh?
아빠랑 '서 믹스-어-랏'이
웃겼지?
Well, Daddy and Sir Mix-A-Lot.
왜? 더 듣고 싶어?
What? What?
You wanna hear some more?
나의 커다란 뱀은
빵빵한 엉덩이를 좋아해
난 아빠도 아냐!
I'm a terrible father.
프렌즈 시즌 9
'로스의 부적절한 랩'
- 너희들 투자에 대해 좀 알아?
- 왜?
- What do you know about investments?
- How come?
돈이 좀 모이기 시작해서
뭐든 해야할것 같아
I'm starting to make good money on the
show, and I should do something with it.
- 지금은 어떻게 하고 있는데?
- 변기 뒤에 테이프로 붙여놨지
- What do you do with your money now?
- It's taped to the back of my toilet tank.
아냐! 돈은 은행에 있어!
로봇이 지키고 있다구!
I didn't say that.
It's in a bank guarded by robots.
- 생각해 본거 있어?
- 아는 사람이
- Do you have any ideas?
- A guy at work got me excited..
에뮤농장 얘기를 해줬는데
관심이 생기더라
about going in on an emu farm.
That'd be kind of cool, huh?
괜찮겠지?
주말엔 에뮤 심는것도 돕고 말야
Pitching in on the weekends,
helping to plant the emus.
에뮤는 새야
식용으로 키우는 거라구
Joe, emus are birds.
You raise them for meat.
새를 먹는대!
Yeah. Right!
새를 어떻게 먹어?
새고기라니!
People eat birds. Bird meat.
새가 입속으로 날아 들어가니?
식당 가서
Do they just fly into your mouth?
Or you go in a restaurant and say:
"튀긴 새 주세요!" 그래?
"Excuse me, I'll have
a bucket of fried bird."
아니면 '날개'요리? 어..
Or maybe just a wing. Or a..
좀더 안전한걸
생각해봐
You should consider something
a little less risky.
요즘 부동산이 괜찮대
I think real estate is
your best investment.
세율도 낮아졌고
주택담보대출은 세금도 공제야
The Fed just lowered the rates, and the
interest on your mortgage is deductible.
그래, 나도 조금은 알아
That's right. I know some stuff.
부동산이라구?
Real estate, huh?
참, 좋은 아파트 내놓은
사람이 누구게? 리처드!
And you know who's selling
a great apartment? Richard!
옛날 애인 소식 잘도 아는
사람이 누구게? 모니카!
And you know whose knowledge of
her ex-boyfriend is shocking? Monica!
아빠가 말씀해주셨어
같이 골프 치시잖아
- My dad told me. They play golf together.
- Well, maybe I'll join them sometime.
나도 언제 같이 쳐야겠는걸
내 클럽이 미끄러져서
I just hope the club doesn't
slip out of my hand..
리처드 콧수염
확 밀어버리면 어쩌나!
and beat the mustache
off his face.
의사 선생님 말이 엠마가
출생시 체중을 두배나 붙여서
And then the doctor said Emma
has doubled her birth weight..
90 백분위수에 들어갔고
곧 고형 음식도 먹을거래
she is in the 90th percentile and she's
gonna start eating solid foods soon.
- 잘됐다!
- 그래
- That's great!
- I know!
- 전엔 무슨 얘기를 했었니?
- 글쎄다
- What did we used to talk about?
- No idea.
옷좀 골라줘, 오늘 저녁
마이크 부모님 뵙기로 했어!
Hi! You have to help me pick a dress.
I'm meeting Mike's parents tonight.
남자친구 부모님이라..
큰 발전이네
Wow, the boyfriend's parents.
That's a big step.
- 정말? 이런일 처음이거든
- 그냥 네 모습 그대로 보여줘
- Really? That hadn't occurred to me.
- They'll love you. Just be yourself.
'어퍼 이스트 사이드'에 사는 분들이
나랑 참 잘도 맞겠다
They live on the Upper East Side
on Park Avenue.
저런, 그대로는 안되겠다
Yeah, she can't be herself.
자, 어느 옷 입을까?
Okay, so, all right, which dress?
- 둘다 아니라고 해도 돼
- 둘다 아냐
- You can say neither.
- Oh, God. Neither.
곱게 말하면 안되냐?
You can say it nicely.
미안해, 우리랑 쇼핑 가자
잘될거야
I'm sorry. We'll take you shopping.
It'll be fine.
우리만 믿어, 또 남자 부모님에
대해선 내가 선수잖니
You are in such good hands,
and I am so good with meeting parents.
아버지는 좀 띄워주는게 좋아
주책스럽게는 말고
With the father, you wanna flirt a little,
but not in a gross way.
"어머, 핀처씨, 월리스가
누구 닮아 미남인지 알겠네요"
Just kind of like, "Mr. Pinzer, I can
see where Wallace gets his good looks."
- 월리스 핀처랑 사귀었어?
- 걔가 내 대신 SAT 봐줬잖아
- You went out with Wallace Pinzer?
- He took the SATs for me.
어쩐지! 네 점수치고
너무 높다 했어!
- I knew you didn't get a 1400!
- Yeah, well, duh! I mean..
당연하지!
어머니 쪽은 어떻게 하지?
So now, what about with Mike's mom?
어머니 쪽은 말야.. 아들이 얼마나
대단한지 끊임없이 얘기해줘
Well, with the mother, just constantly
tell her how amazing her son is.
나처럼 해, 엄마들은
나 좋아해, 로스 어머님은
Take it from me. Moms love me.
Ross' mom one time actually said..
나같은 딸 있으면
좋겠다고 하신적도 있어
I am like the daughter
that she never had.
뭐라구 하셨다구?
- She said what?
- She's like the daughter she never had.
레이첼 같은 딸 있으면
좋겠다고 하셨대
잘들어
Listen.
피비가 마이크 부모님 만난대서
봐주고 왔어
I just got Phoebe all dressed
to meet Mike's parents.
얼마나 긴장하는지
사랑스럽더라!
She's so nervous. It's so sweet.
그거 알아?
오늘 엠마가 웃었어
Guess what. I made Emma laugh today.
뭐라구?
난 못 봤는데!
You what? And I missed it..
멍청한 히피 계집애
옷 챙겨주느라고 못봤잖아!
because I was giving a makeover
to that stupid hippie?!
아주 제대로 웃었다니까
Yeah, and it was like
a real little person laugh too.
이렇게 말야
It was like:
- 이렇게 징그럽진 않았지만
- 알았어
Only not creepy.
- 도대체 뭘로 웃겼어?
- 내가..
- What did you do to make her laugh?
- I..
노래를 불러줬어
Well, I sang. Actually..
정확히는 랩이었지
I rapped..
"베이비 갓 백"
"Baby Got Back."
뭐?
You what?
우리 딸한테..
You sang to our baby daughter..
엉덩이 큰 여자랑 자고 싶어하는
a song about a guy
who likes to have sex..
남자에 관한 랩을 불러줬다구?
with women with giant asses?
생각해보면
You know what,
if you think about it..
건강한 신체 이미지를
권장하는 노래야
it actually promotes
a healthy body image..
'커다란 궁둥이'나
because even big butts..
'주름진 뱃살' 마저도..
or "juicy doubles" are..
제발 엠마 뺏어 가지마
Please don't take her away from me.
어서오세요, 부동산 중개인
캐서린이에요
Hi, come on in.
I'm Catherine, the listing agent.
조이라고 합니다
이 친구는 챈들러구요
Hi, I'm Joey. This is Chandler.
리처드가 이 집을 왜 팔려고 하죠?
파산했나?
So how come Richard's selling
the place? Went bankrupt?
의료사고 냈대요?
자기 콧수염에 숨이 막혔나?
Medical malpractice?
Choked on his own mustache?
훨씬 더 큰집을 사실 거예요
He's buying a much bigger place.
It's got a great view of Central Park..
센트럴 파크가 한눈에
내려다보이는 곳이죠
더 설명 안하셔도 돼요
That's enough out of you.
이 집에 대해
알아야 할게 있나요?
Is there anything we should know
about the place?
가구 모두 포함이에요
조명이 많고 부엌도 새로 했죠
All the appliances are included.
There's a lot of light, a new kitchen.
두분 여기 살면
행복할 거예요
I think you guys would be
very happy here.
아뇨, 아녜요!
우리 같이 안살아요
No, we're not together.
We're definitely not a couple.
커플 아닙니다!
절대로 아니죠!
- 어머, 미안해요
- 괜찮아요
- Okay. Sorry.
- That's all right.
그말이 아주
모욕적이었나 보지?
Wow, you seemed
pretty insulted by that.
내가 너한테 부족하단 거야?
What, I'm not good enough for you?
그얘기 이젠 그만좀 하자
We are not gonna have
this conversation again.
여길봐, 내가 왜
리처드한테 위협을 느끼지?
Look at this place.
Why am I so intimidated by this guy?
폼잡이용 그림에
커다란 남성취향 소파
Pretentious art.
This huge, macho couch.
모니카 잃고 여기 앉아
When we know
all he does is sit around..
하루종일 엉엉 운 주제에!
crying about losing Monica
to a real man.
리처드 여기 없는거 맞지?
- You don't think he's here, do you?
- I don't know.
이 집 괜찮긴 한데
여기사는 내 모습 상상이 안돼
It's a nice place, but I gotta say,
I don't know if I see myself living here.
한번 해볼까?
Well, let me see.
이제 상상이 된다
Yeah, I can see it.
이 비디오 좀 봐!
자기를 뭐라고 생각하는 거야?
Look at these videos.
I mean, who does he think he is?
매그넘 포스, 더티 해리
쿨 핸드 루크..
Magnum Force, Dirty Harry,
Cool Hand Luke.
- 맙소사!
- 왜?
- Oh, my God.
- What?
모니카 이름이 붙은 테이프가 있어!
There's a tape here
with Monica's name on it.
여자이름이 붙은 테이프라면
분명 섹스 테이프일 거야
A tape with a girl's name on it.
It's probably a sex tape.
잠깐!
Wait a minute.
모니카라고 써있네!
This says "Monica."
여긴 리처드 집이잖아!
And this is Richard's apartment.
생각좀 빨리 해라!
Get there faster!
우와! 꼭..
Wow. You look..
우리 엄마 같네요
like my mom.
팬티스타킹도 신었어요!
I'm wearing pantyhose.
- 근사해요! 들어와요
- 그래요
- Great! Come on in.
- Okay.
고마워요
Thank you.
- 세상에! 부자군요!
- 부모님이 부자죠
- Oh, my God. You're rich.
- No, my parents are rich.
그래서요? 언젠가
돌아가실 거잖아요
Well, so? They gotta die someday.
Hello!
안녕하세요?
아빠, 엄마, 피비예요
Mom, Dad, this is Phoebe.
저희 부모님이세요
Phoebe, these are my parents,
Theodore and Bitsy.
안녕하세요?
Theodore, Bitsy..
반갑습니다
what a delight.
- 만나서 반가워요
- 저두요
- It's so nice to finally meet you.
- And you.
집이 예쁘네요
Your home is lovely.
고마워요, 나중에 안내하죠
전부 3층이랍니다
Thank you. I'll give you a tour later.
It's actually three floors.
세상에나!
Holy crap!
거실에 와서 친구들과
인사하겠어요?
Why don't you come meet our friends.
물론 그래야죠
Try and stop me.
뭐하는 거예요?
- What are you doing?
- Trying to get your parents to like me.
부모님 마음에 들려고
애쓰는 중이에요
분명히 좋아하실테니까
이럴 필요 없어요
I'm sure they will,
but you don't have to do this.
진짜 피비를 보여줘요
발음이 이상한 피비말구
I want them to get to know Phoebe,
not "Phoebe."
재밌지 않나요?
It is fun, though, isn't it?
- 알았어요
- 좋아요
- You've got it.
- All right.
그새 입에 붙었네요
It's hard to stop.
신경쓰지 말아요
Well, come on.
피비, 내 친구들이에요
탐과 수 엥겔 부부
Phoebe, these are our friends
Tom and Sue Engel.
- 앉아요, 자기 얘기좀 해봐요
- 그러죠
Phoebe, come sit.
Tell us a little bit about yourself.
- 고향이 어디예요?
- 어, 네
- So where are you from?
- Okay.
말씀드리죠
뉴욕북부에서 났는데
Well, all right.
Originally, I'm from upstate..
엄마가 자살하고
양아빠가 감옥간후
but then my mom killed herself,
and my stepdad went to prison.
뉴욕에 와서 불탄 자동차 안에서
한동안 살았죠
So I moved to the city, where I lived in
a burned-out Buick LeSabre for a while.
괜찮았어요
살만 했다구요
Which was okay. That was okay.
간염에 걸리기 전까지는요
Until I got hepatitis, you know..
어떤 포주가
제입에 침을 뱉는 바람에..
because this pimp spit
in my mouth and..
하지만 다 나았어요
But I got over it.
어쨌든 지금은 프리랜서
맛사지 치료사예요
And, anyway, now I'm
a freelance massage therapist..
수입이 안정적이진 않지만
세금은 안내죠
which isn't always steady money,
but at least I don't pay taxes.
여름은 어디서 보내세요?
So where does everyone summer?
난 이거 안볼거야!
볼 필요없지
I'm not gonna watch it.
I don't need to watch it.
이걸봐서 무슨
좋은일이 있겠어?
I mean, what good could
possibly come from watching it?
내가 볼거란건
세상이 다 알지
Well, we know I'm gonna watch it.
뭐하니?
- Hey, dude, what's up?
- Don't judge me! I'm only human!
뭐라고 하지마!
나도 인간이라구!
그 테이프 가져왔어?
Did you take that tape?
어쩔수 없었어! 네가 결혼했는데
다른 남자 집에서
I had to! Imagine you were married
and you found a tape of your wife..
네 마누라 테이프를
발견했다고 생각해봐
in another guy's apartment. Wouldn't
you need to know what was on it?
너라면 뭐가 찍혔는지
궁금하지 않겠어?
글쎄, 내가 누구랑
결혼했는데?
I don't know. Who am I married to?
어떤 여자겠지!
Some girl.
예뻐?
She hot?
그래
어떻게 날 결혼하게 만들었대?
How did she get me to settle down?
어쨌든 난 볼거야
All right, I'm gonna watch it.
내 생각이랑 다를수도 있어
I mean, it's probably
not even what I think it is.
생각대로 라고 해도 상상만큼
심하지 않을수도 있구
Even if it is, it can't possibly be as
bad as what I'm picturing in my head.
그렇지?
Can it?
경험상 여자가 비디오 찍는걸
허락했을 경우에는..
In my experience,
if a girl says yes to being taped..
갈때까지 갔다고 봐야지
she doesn't say no to much else,
I'll tell you.
- 그럼 네가 대신 봐줘
- 뭐? 뭐라구?
- Then you have to watch it for me.
- What?
조금만 봐줘
분위기 파악할 정도만
Just for a few seconds
so I can know what it is. Please?
좋아! 내가 보고 좋아해도
순전히 네 탓이다!
All right, fine. But if I enjoy this,
you have only yourself to blame!
- 웬 응원소리?
- 그냥 축구경기인데?
- Why am I hearing cheering?
- It's okay. It's just a football game.
- 축구? 그냥 축구?
- 봐, 쓸데없는 걱정이었어
- It's just football?
- You were all worried for nothing.
축구다! 그냥 축구야!
It's football! It's just football!
다행이야! 축구가 재미있어
보기는 난생 처음이다!
This is great! This is the first time
I've ever enjoyed football!
이럴땐 맥주 한잔 해야지?
I think it may be customary to get a beer.
저건..?
What the..?
- 뭐하는 거야?
- 넌 저거 보면 안돼!
- What are you doing?
- You don't wanna see what I just saw!
두사람 뭐해?
What are you guys doing?
세상에!
저거 리처드 아냐!
Oh, my God! Is that Richard?
- 어떡해요! 나 엉망이죠?
- 잘하고 있어요, 정말이에요
- Oh, God, this is not going well.
- No, you're doing fine. Really.
- 아빠하고 얘기좀 해요
- 알았어요
- Why don't you go talk to my dad.
- Okay, okay, okay.
- 계속 내 모습 그대로 해요?
- 그럼요
- Still sure about me being myself?
- Absolutely.
포주의 침 얘기는
조금 덜해도 돼요
Though maybe just
a little less "pimp spit."
저기요, 마이크가 누구 닮아
잘생겼는지 알겠어요
So, Theodore, I can see
where Mike gets his good looks from.
오, 무슨..
Well..
- 체격두요! 매일 운동하시나봐요
- 아니, 매일은 아니고 노력은 하죠
- You must work out all the time.
- Not all the time. I do the best I can.
그러실것 같아요
조심하세요!
Yeah, I bet. Look out!
- 어머, 괜찮으세요?
- 얼마전 수술을 받았어요
- Oh, my God. Are you okay?
- I recently had surgery.
- 정말 죄송해요!
- 괜찮을 거예요
- I'm so sorry.
- No, I'll be fine.
- 꿰맨곳 좀 보고 오겠소
- 정말 정말 죄송해요
- I just should check the stitches.
- I really am sorry.
몰라서 그런걸요
배를 때릴수도 있는거죠
How could you know? Why wouldn't
you punch me in the stomach?
방금 우리 아빠 쳤어요?
Did you just hit my dad?
네, 미안해요! 남자친구 부모님은
처음 뵙는거라..
Yes. I'm sorry. I've never met
a boyfriend's parents before.
그래도 사람은 만나본적
있을거 아녜요?
But, I mean, you have met
humans before, right?
엄마랑 얘기해봐요
Why don't you go talk to my mom.
알았어요, 그럴게요
친절해 보이세요, 얘기해 볼게요
Okay, yeah, your mom.
She looks nice. I can talk to her.
난 아버지 내출혈은 없는지
봐드리고 올게요
You do that, and I'm gonna go check
my dad for signs of internal bleeding.
오늘 초대해 주신거
다시 한번 감사드려요
Bitsy? Listen, I wanted to thank you
again for having me here tonight.
천만에요
Well, not at all.
아드님은 정말
멋진 사람이에요
Also, I just want you to know
what a wonderful man your son is.
- 고마워요, 나도 그렇게 생각해요
- 어떻게 자랐는지 잘 알것 같아요
- Thank you. I think so too.
- It's a testament to how he was raised.
어머님 영향이 큰것 같아요
여자를 아주 존중하거든요
Especially to you,
because he's very respectful of women.
정말 그래요?
- Is he really?
- He is so considerate of my feelings.
그럼요, 제 감정을
아주 잘 이해해줘요
그리고 얼마나 자상한
연인인지 모르실 거예요
You know, I think you'd also like
to know that he is a very gentle lover.
뭐, 뭐라구요?
Excuse me?
아뇨, 오해하지 마세요!
여자 같다는 뜻이 아녜요
No, don't get me wrong.
No, not in like a sissy way.
할때는
When he gets going..
휴가 나온 군인처럼
침대머리판 뽀개질 정도라니까요
he can rattle a headboard
like a sailor on leave.
우리 아들 장하기도 하지
That's.. my boy.
잘했어요
Awesome.
제발 엄마한테도 웃어주라!
Okay, please laugh for Mommy.
Please?
착하지, 웃어봐
Please laugh for Mommy.
재미없니?
Not funny, huh?
꼭 그 거슬리는
Well, so is it..
별난 랩송이어야 해?
only offensive novelty rap?
아니면 보통 랩도 괜찮니?
엄마도 랩 할줄알아
Or maybe just, you know, rap in general.
Because Mommy can rap.
나는 엄마랍니다
잘들어요, 모든 아기들은..
아냐, 난 랩 못해!
I can't rap.
좋아, 아가야, 이건 순전히
널 무지 사랑하기 때문이다
All right, sweetheart. This is
only because I love you so much.
아무한테도 말하면 안돼
And I know that you're
not gonna tell anybody.
난 큰 엉둥이가 좋아!
거짓말은 못해
너희들도 부인 못할걸
개미허리 아가씨가
내게 다가오면..
그래! 바로 그거야!
성공이다!
난 큰 엉덩이가 좋아!
거짓말은 못해
너희들도 부인 못할걸
오, 엠마!
네가 웃는구나!
Emma, you're laughing! You are!
너 '큰 엉덩이'를
정말 좋아하는구나!
You really do like big butts, don't you?
요런 귀여운 별종 같으니!
You beautiful little weirdo.
- 나 왔어!
- 조금만 일찍 오지!
You missed it! She was laughing!
방금 엠마가 웃었어!
굉장해!
It was amazing.
너무 예쁘더라!
세상에서 제일 예쁜 소리였어
It was amazing. It was the most
beautiful, beautiful sound.
알아, 정말 그렇지?
어떻게 웃겼어?
I know, isn't it?
What'd you do to get her to laugh?
그냥 뭐..
이것 저것 해봤지
You know, I just..
A couple of things I tried. Different..
'작은 거미 한마리' 불러줬어
Just sang a little
"The Itsy-Bitsy Spider."
"베이비 갓 백" 불렀지?
You sang "Baby Got Back," didn't you?
다 소용 없더라구!
얜 엉덩이만 좋아해!
Nothing else worked!
That girl is all about the ass!
그리고 다시 코러스예요
And then it goes back to the chorus.
냄새나는 고양이
네탓이 아니란다
그게 노래 끝이에요
Resolve.
And that's the end of the song.
불러보라고 하신분 없지만
I realize you hadn't asked
to hear it..
17분째 아무도 말을 안해서요
but no one had spoken
in 17 minutes.
피비는 멋진 노래를
많이 작곡했어요
Phoebe writes lots of songs. What was
that one you sang the other night?
지난번에 사람들이 다들
좋아했던 그 노래가 뭐였죠?
"변태 퍼레이드"?
"Pervert Parade"?
- "털에 대한 송가"?
- 그만!
- "Ode to a Pubic Hair"?
- Stop.
송아지고기 아녜요?
Oh, God. Is that veal?
피비는 채식주의자라고
말씀드리지 않았나요?
Mom, I thought I told you,
Phoebe's a vegetarian.
아뇨, 괜찮아요
채식주의자긴 하지만
No, that's okay. That's okay.
I mean, I am a vegetarian..
송아지 고기는 먹어요
그럼요, 얼마나 좋아한다구요
except for veal.
Yeah. No. Veal I love.
- 안먹어도돼
- 아뇨
- Phoebe, you don't have to eat that.
- Any baby animals. Kittens, fish babies.
어린 동물은 다 좋아요
새끼 고양이, 새끼붕어
송아지는 특히 더 좋아하죠
But, you know, especially veal.
혈관속을 흐르는
지방덩어리도 좋구요
You know, and this nice vein of fat
running through it.
맛있네요
Yummy.
피비 보시니까
So..
어떠세요?
what do you think?
리처드 집에서 저 테이프를
훔쳐왔다구?
So you stole that tape
from Richard's apartment?
포르노 스타께서
지금 누굴 비난하는 거야?
Listen to the judgment
from the porn star!
저건 결코 누구 보라고..
That tape was never meant
to be seen by..
조이! 이 얘긴 우리 둘이서만
했으면 좋겠다
Joey, I would feel more comfortable
if this conversation were in private.
지금 너랑 나 사이에
비밀이 어디 있다고 그래?
Monica, look, I don't think you and I
have any secrets anymore.
농담할 상황 아니라구?
알았어, 이따보자
Not ready to joke about it yet?
See you later.
대체 이 테이프 왜 가져왔어?
대체 이걸 왜 본거야?
Why in the world would you take this tape?
And why would you watch it?
난 원래 그런 놈이니까!
Because that's who I am. Okay?
리처드 같은 성숙한 인간은 이런것
보고도 아무렇지 않겠지!
I'm sure a man like Richard could see
a tape like that and not be bothered.
자기 친구들과
It'd just be another saucy anecdote..
콧수염 만지며 나눌 멋진
얘깃거리에 불과할 테니까!
for him to share at his men's club
over brandy and mustaches.
지금 자기 콧수염 못길러서
이러는 거야?
Is all of this about you not being able
to grow a mustache?
자기와 리처드 때문이야
그사람 자길 못 잊었어!
This is about you and Richard.
He's clearly not over you.
테이프를 그대로 둔건
보고싶을 때마다 보기 위해서라구!
He keeps a tape so he can
look at it whenever he wants.
그거 슬픈 일 아냐?
얼마나 청승맞은 짓이냐구!
Isn't that sad?
Can't you see how pathetic that is?
그사람 질투할게 아니라
동정해야 해!
Don't be jealous.
You should feel bad for him.
그래, 참 가엾은 리처드지!
Yeah, well, poor Richard, he..
나도 콧수염 기를수 있어!
I can grow a mustache.
챈들러, 이건
우리 문제가 아냐
This is not our problem. We have
each other. That's all that matters.
우린 지금 함께 있잖아
그게 중요한 거야
하지만 자기가 카우보이 부츠 신고
리처드랑 뒹구는게
But I just keep picturing you rolling
around with him, with your..
자꾸 생각나!
cowboy boots in the air.
카우보이 부츠? 나 그런거
신은적 없는데?
Cowboy boots? I've never worn
cowboy boots in my whole life.
좋아! 틀어!
끝을 보고 싶으니까!
Good, good. Play more
because I wanna see how it ends.
- 저건 나 아냐!
- 뭐?
- That's not me!
- What?
자기 아니네!
세상이 다시 밝아졌다!
That's not you! Life is good again!
잘한다, 카우걸!
Ride 'em, cowgirl!
나쁜 자식, 내 테이프 위에
덮어 씌웠잖아!
That bastard taped over me!
그래서 기분 나빠?
Is that a problem?
이건 모욕이야!
웬만하면 공테이프 좀 사시지!
It's just so insulting.
Spring for a new blank tape, doctor!
하지만 중요한건
우리가 지금 함께 있다는 거지?
Yes, but the important thing is
that we have each other, right?
그래, 하지만..
너무하잖아!
Well, yeah. It's just so rude!
- 우리 버전이 훨씬 더..
- 끝까지 다 얘기할 생각이야?!
- And the way we did it was a lot better..
- Are you going to finish that sentence?
그 여자 뭐가 좋다는 건지
모르겠군
I can't imagine what he sees in her.
차라리 약물중독이던
옛날 며느리가 다 그립네요
She actually makes me miss
that pill-popping ex-wife of his.
오, 마이크
Hello, dear.
- 무슨 얘기 중이세요?
- 그냥 수다지, 뭐
- What's going on?
- We were just chitchatting.
- 네 친구는 어때?
- 좀 나아졌어요
- How's your friend?
- A little better.
참, 누가 뉴욕에 다시 돌아오는줄
아니? 탐과 수의 딸, 젠이 온단다
Do you know who's moving back into
town? Tom and Sue's daughter, Jen.
기억나지? 사랑스럽고
예의 바르고 아직 혼자란다
You remember her, Michael.
She's lovely, well-behaved and single.
- 관심 없어요
- 마이크, 터놓고 얘기해보자
- I'm not interested.
- Please, darling, let's be honest.
저 애랑은 재미보고 싶을때
언제든지 볼수 있어
You can have all the sailor fun
you want with that one.
- 현실을 생각해
- 그만하세요
- But let's be real.
- All right, stop.
오늘 피비 행동은 두분 마음에
들기위한 것이었어요
All Phoebe has done is try and get you
to like her. Maybe it's not clear..
좀 지나친 점도 있었지만
나름대로 최선을 다했다구요
but she did her best.
그래요, 피비는 두분과는
좀 다른 사람이에요
- She's a little different than you are.
- Michael, a pimp spit in her mouth.
마이크, 포주가 입에
침을 뱉었다잖니!
그래서요? 제가 괜찮다는데
무슨 상관이에요?
So what? If I can get past that,
it shouldn't bother you.
피비를 좋아하실 필요도 없어요
제가 좋아한다는 것만 인정해 주세요!
You don't have to like her.
Just accept the fact that I do.
제가 사랑하는 여자
그렇게 무시하지 마시구요!
If you can't even be civil
to the woman I love..
- 어떤 여자?
- 어떤 여자라구요?
- The woman you what?
- Yeah, the woman you what?
사랑하는 여자라구요
The woman I love.
사랑해요
I love you.
이런말 부모님과 손님들 앞에서
Something I shouldn't say for
the first time, in front of my parents..
처음 하면 안되지만..
and Tom and Sue.
저렇게 따분한 분들
내 평생 처음봐요
Who are, by the way, the most sinfully
boring people I've ever met in my life.
- 나도 사랑해요
- 정말?
- I love you too.
- You do?
그럼요
굉장하죠?
How great is this?
- 우리 나갈까요?
- 좋아요
Wanna get out of here?
- 저녁 잘 먹었습니다
- 즐거웠어요
- Mom, Dad. Thanks for dinner.
- I had a great time.
모든게 최고급이었어요!
It was really top-drawer.
And here's something rich.
그중에 제일 사치스러웠던 건요
화장실이 13개나 되는데
전 옷장에 토했지 뭐예요
Thirteen bathrooms in this place,
I threw up in the coat closet.
안녕!
Ta-ta!
춤추는거 봤어
연애는 집어치워
끈적끈적 축축
스포츠카처럼 달려
- 어이, 친구들
- 예!
- 친구들!
네 여자친구
엉덩이도 괜찮니?
물론!
- 그럼 흔들어!
- 흔들어!
엉덩이를 흔들어!
베이비 갓 백!
처음부터 한번 더!
One more time from the top!
난 큰 엉덩이가 좋아!
거짓말은 못해
너희들도 부인 못할걸..
레이첼, 제발!
애한테 무슨 짓이야!
Rachel, please!
That is so inappropriate!